[{
        "question": "ques_non_tech0",
        "answer": " John Dalton"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech1",
        "answer": "280"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech2",
        "answer": "Thursday"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech3",
        "answer": "20+10+5+4"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech4",
        "answer": " sorry for wasting time"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech5",
        "answer": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech6",
        "answer": "31, 962, 29791, 923522"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech7",
        "answer": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech8",
        "answer": " Google Cloud Programming"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech9",
        "answer": "MediaTek Helio G85"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech10",
        "answer": " iPhone XS"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech11",
        "answer": "hacktober"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech12",
        "answer": "A=3.5,B=6.5,C=11.5,D=5.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech13",
        "answer": "macros"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech14",
        "answer": "Christoph Martin Wieland"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech15",
        "answer": "+="
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech16",
        "answer": "% / * ="
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech17",
        "answer": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech18",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech19",
        "answer": "No of milliseconds in a Day"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech20",
        "answer": "Brown"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech21",
        "answer": "Clyde"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech22",
        "answer": "SHOW PEARS BUS ARE"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech23",
        "answer": "Micromax"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech24",
        "answer": "8 tentacles on an octopus"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech25",
        "answer": "64 squares on a chess board"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech26",
        "answer": "13112221"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech27",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech28",
        "answer": "elgoog.im"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_non_tech29",
        "answer": "Insanity"
    } {
        "question": "ques_non_tech30",
        "answer": "19"
    }
]